(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Daniel had a project for school.
It was on planets.
He had to research one planet and write
a report.
His planet was Mars.
He decided to go to the library and
borrow books.
He borrowed three books.
He saw his friends there.
They went to lunch.
He also went to lunch.
After the lunch, he realized that he left
the books at the lunchroom.
He went back.
They were no longer there.
Daniel panicked.
He did not want to pay for the
books.
His parents would get mad at him.
He looked everywhere.
Later, his friends told him maybe they were
at the library.
Daniel went to the library.
He found the books there.
He left them there before he went to
eat.
Daniel was so relieved.